<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">Dr.D.Y.P. User</string>

    <string name="bold" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lorabold</string>
    <string name="medium" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/loramedium</string>
    <string name="regular" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/loraregular</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="clase">Close</string>
    <string name="about_collage1">Dr. D. Y. Patil Educational Federation was established in 2014 by Dr. Sushant Patil under the guidance of Padmashree Dr. D. Y. Patil, former governor of Tripura, Bihar and West Bengal and a well-known educationist and philanthropist from Kolhapur, Maharashtra. Dr. D. Y. Patil Educational Federation is a part of Dr. D. Y. Patil group. Dr. D Y Patil is the leading group in India imparting comprehensive education. The group is having 31 years of experience in education with 200 institutes across India and 4 universities in Maharashtra. Dr. D. Y. Patil group have almost 200000+ most brilliant students and 500000 Alumni across the world. Dr. D. Y. Patil is offering almost 1000 courses and programs. Courses at Dr. D. Y. Patil Educational Federation are designed to equip students with skills to meet the challenges and opportunities of the corporate world. Our value based learning model provides transformational experience that fosters professional, intellectual, and personal development.</string>
    <string name="about_collage">Dr. D. Y. Patil Prathishthan’s, Dr. D. Y. Patil College of Engineering and Innovation, Varale, Talegaon, Pune was established in 1984 in Pimpri and later shifted to Akurdi complex in 2001, which is in the vicinity of Pimpri Chinchwad Industrial area, one of the biggest Industrial belts in Asia.
        The college spreads over 10 acres of land with seven Engineering disciplines. This Institute is approved by AICTE, New Delhi and is affiliated to the Savitribai Phule Pune University.

The college has excellent &amp; ambient infrastructure with well-equipped laboratories. Well-qualified, motivated, and dedicated faculty members are serving in the Institute. Students are encouraged to actively participate in National and State level co-curricular and extracurricular activities.</string>
</resources>